Sadie Sink
you are in the film
Spider-Man
Brand New Day
Correct
V
1"
VI
V1
You play the
films main
villain
_
have t1o
see
d see
1 see
"d see'
"d see
"d ses !
ad see
and se9
You play
Spider-Mans
other love
interest
Gwen Stacy
_
I
L
I lless We
rind oui
You play Mayday
Parker the
daughter of
Peter and MJ
who eventually
becomes
Spider-Girl
1i
dont know
You
You play
Punishers
sidekick
Rachel Cole
i
!wer ind ou in
eaters
You play
Firestar who
could be
Spider-Mans
first superhero
love interest
_
1二
二
三
wiu knowe?
i
_
This is the most
popular
internet theory
You play Jean
Grey who will
bring a new era
.of X-Men mutants
into the MCU
_
wwnt you e
Lin know?
L Gon
Oh my God
That is how you do it
That is a pro
You are a pro